A Guide to the Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller records, Welfare Interests - General Files, Series P FA325
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Aid for the Blind
  - Aid for the Blind - John Milton Society for the Blind, 1948-1959 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contributed to expenses of Oriental trip by Helen Keller, 1948. Later appeals were declined. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, Helen Keller.
    75.9
  - Aid for the Blind - John Milton Society for the Blind - Helen Keller, 1897-1911 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Aid for the Blind - American Printing House for the Blind, 1944-1961 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    75.10
  - Aid for the Blind - American Printing House for the Blind, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 0071A)
  - Aid for the Blind - National Society for the Prevention of Blindness, 1932-1961 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    Contributions by Abby Aldrich Rockefeller; other appeals were declined. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, Dana S. Creel, Abby Aldrich Rockefeller.
    75.11
- Charities
  - Charities - Charity Organization Society, 1899-1939 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    Program and policies of Society; John D. Rockefeller, Jr. interest in merger of C.O.S. and Association for the Improvement of the Condition of the Poor. Contributions. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Sr., John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Frederick T. Gates, Starr J. Murphy, Thomas B. Appleget, Arthur W. Packard.
    23
  - Charities - Charity Organization Society, 1908-1941 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Charities - Community Service Society, 1939-1961 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    Merger of Charity Organization Society and Association for the Improvement of the Condition of the Poor; office studies of new organization. Family contributions to new organization. Brothers Fund gifts. Blanchette Hooker Rockefeller served as Vice-Chair of the Board. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Arthur W. Packard, Dana S. Creel, John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
  - Charities - Community Service Society, 1939-1961 (Box 7, Folder 75A)
    Correspondents include David Rockefeller.
  - Charities - Community Service Society - Contributions, 1936-1961 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Charities - Community Service Society - W. H. Matthews Memorial, 1947-1949 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Charities - Community Service Society - Boys Bureau, 1932-1947 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    John D. Rockefeller 3rd's service in Bureau to aid delinquent and stranded boys. Studies of delinquency problem. John D. Rockefeller 3rd resignation from Bureau, 1946. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Leonard Harrison, Alfred Smith, G. M. Hallworks.
    23.1
  - Charities - Community Service Society - Boys Bureau - John D. Rockefeller 3rd Contributions, 1932-1947 (Box 8, Folder 79)
    Annual gifts.
  - Charities - Community Service Society - Boys Bureau - Delinquency Statement, 1938-1939 (Box 8, Folder 80)
    John D. Rockefeller 3rd's drafts of paper.
  - Charities - Community Service Society - Boys Bureau - John D. Rockefeller 3rd Article, 1940-1941 (Box 8, Folder 81)
    Paper on delinquents written for New York Times, 1940. Appeared also in "Readers Digest."
  - Charities - Community Service Society - Boys Bureau - Delinquency Report, 1932-1939 (Box 8, Folder 82)
    Preparation of a book called "Youth in Toils." John D. Rockefeller 3rd's comments on draft and purpose of the study; other comments on early drafts; John D. Rockefeller 3rd's introduction for study. Publication; comments. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Pryor Grant, Leonard Harrison.
    23.1A
  - Charities - Community Service Society - Boys Bureau - Delinquency Report - Publicity, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 83)
    Reviews and clippings, Associated Press release.
  - Charities - Community Service Society - Boys Bureau - Delinquency Report - MacMillan Company, 1937-1943 (Box 8, Folder 84)
    Publishing arrangements.
  - Charities - Community Service Society - "Youth in the Toils", 1938 (Box 8, Folder 0084A)
    23.1B
  - Charities - Community Service Society - "Youth in the Toils", 1938 (Box 8, Folder 0084B)
  - Charities - Community Service Society - "Youth in the Toils" - Acknowledgement Letters, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 85)
    Distribution of copies of book. Letters of comment on book arranged alphabetically. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
  - Charities - Community Service Society - "Youth in the Toils" - Lists, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Charities - Community Service Society - Boys Bureau - Delinquency Report - Miscellaneous Letters, 1938-1941 (Box 9, Folder 87)
    Appeals to John D. Rockefeller 3rd resulting from crime study. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
    23.1C
  - Charities - Community Service Society - Boys Bureau - Delinquency Report - Board of Regents Study, 1938-1939 (Box 9, Folder 88)
    John D. Rockefeller 3rd gave $3,000 for delinquency study; funds returned when study was cancelled. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
  - Charities - Community Service Society - Boys Bureau - Delinquency Report - Committee of the American Law Institute, 1937-1941 (Box 9, Folder 89)
    John D. Rockefeller 3rd contributed to Institute study of criminal justice in the United States. Study's recommended changes in handling criminals. Comments on committee's work and report. Contributions to work from other sources. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd, T. J. Ross, Leonard Harrison, William D. Lewis.
    23.1D
  - Charities - Community Service Society - Boys Bureau - Delinquency Report - Committee of the American Law Institute - Addresses on Youth Correction Authority Act, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 90)
    Speeches by Leonard Harrison and James Bennett on justice for youthful criminals.
  - Charities - American Law Institute - Youth Correction Authority Act, 1940-1949 (Box 9, Folder 91)
    Drafts of model act creating a Youth Correction Authority.
  - Charities - American Law Institute - Contribution Letters, 1938-1942 (Box 9, Folder 92)
    John D. Rockefeller 3rd wrote asking for contributions to finance Institute's study of youthful offenders. Letters of gift and declination filed alphabetically. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
  - Charities - American Law Institute - Memos and Contribution Appeals, 1938-1941 (Box 10, Folder 93)
    Lists of people approached by John D. Rockefeller 3rd for contributions.
  - Charities - American Law Institute - John D. Rockefeller 3rd Contributions, 1937-1952 (Box 10, Folder 94)
    John D. Rockefeller 3rd contributions for special expenses, public relations expenses, and toward model law study. Program terminated in 1952.
  - Charities - American Law Institute, 1941-1949 (Box 10, Folder 95)
    Work of Institute; passage of state laws on criminal justice; Federal Youth Correction Act. John D. Rockefeller 3rd's interest and contributions; publication of studies on delinquency. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd, William D. Lewis, John R. Ellingston.
    23.1D2
  - Charities - American Law Institute, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 96)
  - Charities - American Law Institute, 1950-1959 (Box 10, Folder 97)
  - Charities - American Law Institute - Contributions, 1940-1942, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 98)
    John D. Rockefeller 3rd letters appealing for contributions to Institute's educational program for improving legal treatment of youthful criminals. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
    23.1D3
  - Charities - American Law Institute - Contributions, 1940-1950 (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Charities - American Law Institute - Contributions, 1941-1948 (Box 11, Folder 100)
  - Charities - American Law Institute - Contributions - Commonwealth Fund, 1938-1941 (Box 11, Folder 101)
    Contributions to Institute by Fund.
  - Charities - American Law Institute - Magazine Article, 1940-1942 (Box 11, Folder 102)
    John D. Rockefeller 3rd prepared article on ways to reduce juvenile crime. Attempts to place it in "Readers Digest" and "Colliers." Published in "Life," October 1942.
    23.1D4
  - Charities - American Law Institute - Magazine Article, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 103)
    Related Archival Materials note
    See also Box 56, Folder 627.
  - Charities - American Law Institute - Insurance Companies, 1941-1947 (Box 11, Folder 104)
    John D. Rockefeller 3rd assisted Institute in approaching insurance companies for gifts. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd, William D. Lewis.
    23.1D5
  - Charities - American Law Institute - Insurance Companies, 1941-1948 (Box 11, Folder 105)
  - Charities - Committee on Youth and Justice, 1939-1946 (Box 11, Folder 106)
    Standing committee of Community Service Society, grew out of work of Boys Bureau; program and objectives, search for financial support. Accomplishments of the Committee. Copies of "Correctional Treatment of Youth Offenders" and "Chaos in Sentencing Youth Offenders." Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Leonard V. Harrison, Arthur W. Packard.
    23.1F
  - Charities - Committee on Youth and Justice, 1942-1945 (Box 11, Folder 107)
  - Charities - Committee on Youth and Justice, 1939-1942 (Box 11, Folder 108)
  - Charities - Committee on Youth and Justice - Contributions, 1940-1947 (Box 12, Folder 109)
    By John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
  - Charities - Committee on Youth and Justice - Contributions, 1939-1941 (Box 12, Folder 110)
  - Charities - Judge Baker Guidance Center, 1939-1954 (Box 12, Folder 111)
    John D. Rockefeller 3rd contribution to study for improving child guidance work center in Boston. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd, William Healy.
    23.1G
  - Charities - Magistrates' and Other Courts, 1938-1941 (Box 12, Folder 112)
    Work of Social Service Bureau attached to Magistrate's Court. John D. Rockefeller 3rd declined appeals to participate in work. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Arthur W. Packard, Mrs. Sidney Borg.
    23.1H
    See also Box 56, Folder 629.
  - Charities - Magistrates' and Other Courts, 1938-1941 (Box 12, Folder 0112A)
  - Charities - Delinquency Study - Committee - General, 1940-1941 (Box 12, Folder 113)
    Creation of a committee to work for New York State change in laws regulating youthful criminals. Copy of "The Forgotten Adolescent" published by the New York Law Society. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd, John Barker Waite, Leonard V. Harrison, Timothy Pfeiffer.
    23.1J
  - Charities - Delinquency Study - Committee - Meeting, June 13, 1940 (Box 12, Folder 114)
  - Charities - Youth Correction Authority Act - New York Legislation, 1941-1945 (Box 12, Folder 115)
    New York bill based on American Law Institute model bill introduced in legislature by Thomas Desmond. Passed Senate; defeated in House. Opposed by Thomas Dewey as too expensive. No action as of 1945. Copies of the bill. Copies of "Preventing Criminal Careers," and "Crime Doesn't Pay" by the Youth Correction Authority. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Thomas Desmond, Arthur W. Packard, Leonard V. Harrison.
    23.1J1
  - Charities - Youth Correction Authority Act - New York Legislation, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 116)
  - Charities - Committee on Youth and Justice, 1941-1943 (Box 12, Folder 117)
    Committee to work for New York State changes in laws re juvenile delinquency (New York State Committee on the Youth Correction Authority Plan). Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Arthur W. Packard, Arthur MacCormick.
    23.1J2
  - Charities - Committee on Youth and Justice - Leonard Harrison Article, 1942-1943 (Box 12, Folder 118)
    "Prisons Cost Too Much."
  - Charities - Chicago Area Projects, 1939-1941 (Box 12, Folder 119)
    23.1K
  - Charities - Chicago Area Projects - Industrial Areas Foundation, 1941-1946 (Box 13, Folder 120)
  - Charities - Chicago Area Projects - Clifford Shaw, 1938-1939 (Box 13, Folder 121)
    Reports on the "Back of the Yards" project in Chicago. Criticisms of report on project for combating delinquency.
  - Charities - Greater New York Fund, 1938-1950 (Box 13, Folder 122)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. was an honorary sponsor, 1938 Campaign. Winthrop Rockefeller was Chairman for the 1939 Campaign. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s letters to Winthrop Rockefeller encouraging him and discussing his business career. Memos re business's charity obligations. Assessment of the campaign's reorganization. Speeches by E. R. Stettinius, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Henry Ford II, Howard Rusk. John D. Rockefeller 3rd solicited firms for gifts until 1956. Correspondents include Winthrop Aldrich, James Blaine, Walter Gifford, E. R. Stettinius, Henry Ford II, Edgar B. Young, Arthur Jones, Arthur W. Packard, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Winthrop Rockefeller.
    23.2
    See also Box 56, Folder 630.
  - Charities - Greater New York Fund, 1951-1958 (Box 13, Folder 123)
  - Charities - Greater New York Fund, 1951-1958 (Box 13, Folder 0123A)
  - Charities - Greater New York Fund - John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Address, February 24, 1938 (Box 13, Folder 124)
  - Charities - Greater New York Fund - Waldorf Dinner, May 2, 1938 (Box 13, Folder 125)
  - Charities - Greater New York Fund - Meeting, Union Club, May 8, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 126)
  - Charities - Greater New York Fund - Campaigns, 1939 (Box 13, Folder 127)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. and John D. Rockefeller 3rd sponsor various campaign dinners and solicit gifts. Conflict between Fund and Welfare Council. Statements by Herbert Hoover, John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Cardinal Spellman. Nelson A. Rockefeller declination of 1956 Chairmanship. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Arthur Jones, John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Cardinal Spellman, Harry Truman, Dwight Eisenhower, Herbert Hoover.
  - Charities - Greater New York Fund - Campaigns, 1948-1952 (Box 13, Folder 128)
  - Charities - Greater New York Fund - Campaigns, 1952-1958 (Box 13, Folder 129)
  - Charities - Greater New York Fund - Campaigns - Labor Unions, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 130)
    John D. Rockefeller 3rd headed campaign and sought to get more union participation.
  - Charities - Greater New York Fund - Contributions, 1938-1942 (Box 13, Folder 131)
    Business contributions solicited by John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  - Charities - Greater New York Fund - Contributions, 1938-1942 (Box 13, Folder 0131A)
  - Charities - Greater New York Fund - Contributions - Family Contributions, 1942-1961 (Box 14, Folder 132)
    Office contributions, including the brothers' gifts.
  - Charities - Greater New York Fund - Contributions - Family Contributions, 1942-1961 (Box 14, Folder 0132A)
  - Charities - Greater New York Fund - Clippings, Printed Material, 1938-1957 (Box 14, Folder 133)
    Brochures for 1949 Campaign, editorials, etc.
  - Charities - Welfare Council of New York City - Better Times, Committee for Coordination, 1932-1943 (Box 14, Folder 134)
    Search for methods of coordinating welfare agency activities in New York City. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, N. R. Deardarff.
    23.3
  - Charities - Welfare Council of New York City - Utopia House, 1927-1938 (Box 14, Folder 135)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contributions to home for children of Negro working mothers which provided low-cost lunches and daytime activities. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Thomas B. Appleget, Arthur W. Packard, C. C. Huitt.
  - Charities - Welfare Council of New York City, 1923-1933 (Box 14, Folder 136)
    Council trying to develop mutual understanding and coordination among New York City welfare and health organizations. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contributions. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, Willard S. Richardson, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
    See also Box 56, Folder 626.
  - Charities - Community Council of Greater New York, Inc., 1941 (Box 14, Folder 137)
    (Welfare Council of New York City.) Organized to coordinate welfare activities on city-wide scale. Internal disagreements over policy; birth control controversy and withdrawal of Catholic charities from Council. Reorganized as Community Council, 1956. Rockefeller contributions and participation. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, Dana S. Creel, Arthur Jones, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
  - Charities - Community Council of Greater New York, Inc., 1942-1953 (Box 14, Folder 138)
  - Charities - Community Council of Greater New York, Inc., 1942-1953 (Box 14, Folder 0138A)
  - Charities - Community Council of Greater New York, Inc., 1953-1961 (Box 14, Folder 139)
  - Charities - Community Council of Greater New York, Inc., 1953-1961 (Box 14, Folder 0139A)
  - Charities - Community Council of Greater New York, Inc. - John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Award, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 140)
    (Welfare Council of New York City.) John D. Rockefeller Jr. cited by Welfare council for his help.
    See also Box 56, Folder 631.
  - Charities - Community Council of Greater New York, Inc. - Contributions, 1937-1944 (Box 14, Folder 141)
    (Welfare Council of New York City.) Rockefeller Brothers Fund and family contributions to Welfare Council and Community Council. Correspondents include Nelson A. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Laurance S. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Arthur W. Packard, Dana S. Creel.
  - Charities - Community Council of Greater New York, Inc. - Contributions, 1945-1959 (Box 15, Folder 142)
  - Charities - Community Council of Greater New York, Inc. - Street Clubs Project, 1946-1950 (Box 15, Folder 143)
    (Welfare Council of New York City.) John D. Rockefeller 3rd gift toward cost of Welfare Council study of gangs. Progress of work with street gangs in Harlem. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
  - Charities - Community Council of Greater New York, Inc. - Unemployment Correspondence, 1930-1932 (Box 15, Folder 144)
    (Welfare Council of New York City.)
    23.31
  - Charities - Community Council of Greater New York, Inc. - Unemployment Pledge, November 21, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 145)
    (Welfare Council of New York City.) John D. Rockefeller, Jr. gave $5,000 for emergency unemployment relief through Council.
  - Charities - Institute for Crippled Children and Disabled Men, 1928-1961 (Box 15, Folder 146)
    Started by Red Cross, then taken over by independent committee. Served both soldiers and civilians. Appealed to family for aid. Correspondents include John D. rockefeller, Jr., Laurance S. Rockefeller, Arthur W. Packard, Jeremiah Milbank.
    23.4
  - Charities - Institute for Crippled Children and Disabled Men - Contributions, 1920-1961 (Box 15, Folder 147)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contributions, 1920-1933. John D. Rockefeller 3rd contribution, 1949. Mary French Rockefeller contribution, 1961.
  - Charities - Brooklyn Bureau of Charities, 1909-1926 (Box 15, Folder 148)
    The organization's name changed from Brooklyn Bureau of Charities to Brooklyn Bureau of Social Service in 1945. John D. Rockefeller, Sr. began contributing when Starr J. Murphy demonstrated that Brooklyn really was part of New York City. Contributions by John D. Rockefeller, Sr., John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial, Davison Fund, Rockefeller Foundation for the prevention of tuberculosis and blindness, family counseling, general unemployment relief, etc. Reports on Bureau. Memo on Davison Fund role in local welfare. Correspondents include Starr J. Murphy, Willard S. Richardson, Arthur W. Packard, Thomas B. Appleget, Judge W. Bruce Cobb.
    23.5
  - Charities - Brooklyn Bureau of Charities, 1934-1960 (Box 15, Folder 149)
  - Charities - Brooklyn Bureau of Charities - Courts Committee, 1926-1933 (Box 15, Folder 150)
    The organization's name changed from Brooklyn Bureau of Charities to Brooklyn Bureau of Social Service in 1945. Aims to improve local court facilities and administration. Reports on Committee. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. gifts, 1926-1928.
  - Charities - Brooklyn Bureau of Charities - Contributions, 1945-1959 (Box 15, Folder 151)
    The organization's name changed from Brooklyn Bureau of Charities to Brooklyn Bureau of Social Service in 1945. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. gave $1,000 annually.
  - Charities - Proposed Consolidation of Charities of New York City, 1907-1914 (Box 16, Folder 152)
    Starr J. Murphy proposed a study to consider coordination of major New york City charities, efforts to have the Rockefeller Foundation finance such coordination. Idea dropped in 1914. Correspondents include Starr J. Murphy, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
    23.6
  - Charities - Catholic Charities, 1929-1961 (Box 16, Folder 153)
    Contributions by John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Davison Fund, and Rockefeller Brothers Fund to annual campaigns. One small gift by Nelson A. Rockefeller to Little Sisters of the Poor. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Arthur W. Packard.
  - Charities - Catholic Charities, 1929-1961 (Box 16, Folder 0153A)
  - Charities - Catholic Charities - Contributions, 1929-1951 (Box 16, Folder 154)
  - Charities - Catholic Charities - Contributions, 1952-1960 (Box 16, Folder 155)
  - Charities - Brooklyn Federation of Jewish Charities, 1916-1936 (Box 16, Folder 156)
    John D. Rockefeller, Sr. and John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contributions. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Sr., Starr J. Murphy, Arthur W. Packard, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
    23.7
  - Charities - Jewish Organizations of New York City, 1919-1920 (Box 16, Folder 157)
    John D. Rockefeller, Sr. gives $50,000, John D. Rockefeller, Jr. gives $25,000 toward special building campaign. Correspondents include Willard S. Richardson, John D. Rockefeller, Sr., John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
    23.7H
  - Charities - State Charities Aid Association, 1899-1925 (Box 16, Folder 158)
    Office studies of projects of State Association. Support for special studies of welfare problems with destitute children, hospitals, and alms houses. John D. Rockefeller, Sr. and John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contributions. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Sr., Starr J. Murphy, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Arthur W. Packard.
    23.8
  - Charities - State Charities Aid Association, 1920-1961 (Box 16, Folder 159)
  - Charities - State Charities Aid Association - Public Health Campaign, 1915 (Box 16, Folder 160)
    John D. Rockefeller, Sr. contributes to campaign for legislation regulating charities.
  - Charities - State Charities Aid Association - Committee on Occupation, 1917-1918 (Box 16, Folder 161)
    John D. Rockefeller, Sr. contributes to cost of training programs in municipal hospitals.
  - Charities - State Charities Aid Association - Children's Department, 1910-1920 (Box 16, Folder 162)
    Abby Aldrich Rockefeller and John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contributions for needy children.
  - Charities - State Charities Aid Association - Cities Emergency Survey, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 163)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contributed to cost of unemployment needs survey.
  - Charities - State Charities Aid Association - Emergency Relief Studies, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 164)
  - Charities - State Charities Aid Association - Child Placing and Adoption Committee, 1933-1959 (Box 17, Folder 165)
  - Charities - State Charities Aid Association - Child Placing and Adoption Committee, 1946-1954 (Box 17, Folder 0165A)
  - Charities - State Charities Aid Association - Endowment Fund - Correspondence, 1927-1934 (Box 17, Folder 166)
  - Charities - State Charities Aid Association - Endowment Fund - Pledge, January 25, 1929, 1930-1934 (Box 17, Folder 167)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. pledges $500,000 conditionally, but drive failed to reach goal and only $65,000 paid on pledge. Correspondents include Arthur Woods, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Thomas B. Appleget, Thomas M. Debevoise, Arthur W. Packard.
  - Charities - State Charities Aid Association - Contributions, 1929-1940 (Box 17, Folder 168)